Guide to the Gertrude Stein and Alice B. Toklas Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Restricted Fragile Papers, 0.5; (1 box)
  - PHOTOGRAPHS
    - Photograph(s) from Box 147, folder 3392 (Box 173, Folder 4363)
    - Photograph(s) from Box 147, folder 3393 (Box 173, Folder 4364)
    - Photograph(s) from Box 147, folder 3394 (Box 173, Folder 4365)
    - Photograph(s) from Box 147, folder 3395 (Box 173, Folder 4366)
    - Photograph(s) from Box 147, folder 3396 (Box 173, Folder 4367)
    - Photograph(s) from Box 147, folder 3398 (Box 173, Folder 4368)
    - Photograph(s) from Box 147, folder 3401 (Box 173, Folder 4369)
    - Photograph(s) from Box 147, folder 3403 (Box 173, Folder 4370)
    - Photograph(s) from Box 147, folder 3404 (Box 173, Folder 4371)
    - Photograph(s) from Box 147, folder 3405 (Box 173, Folder 4372)
    - Photograph(s) from Box 147, folder 3406 (Box 173, Folder 4373)
    - Photograph(s) from Box 147, folder 3407 (Box 173, Folder 4374)
    - Photograph(s) from Box 147, folder 3409 (Box 173, Folder 4375)
    - Photograph(s) from Box 147, folder 3410 (Box 173, Folder 4376)
    - Photograph(s) from Box 147, folder 3411 (Box 173, Folder 4377)
    - Photograph(s) from Box 147, folder 3413 (Box 173, Folder 4378)
    - Photograph(s) from Box 147, folder 3415 (Box 173, Folder 4379)
    - Photograph(s) from Box 147, folder 3416 (Box 173, Folder 4380)
    - Photograph(s) from Box 147, folder 3417 (Box 173, Folder 4381)
    - Photograph(s) from Box 147, folder 3418 (Box 173, Folder 4382)
    - Photograph(s) from Box 154, folder 3799 (Box 173, Folder 4383)
    - Photograph(s) from Box 154, folder 3800 (Box 173, Folder 4384)
    - Photograph(s) from Box 154, folder 3801 (Box 173, Folder 4385)
    - Photograph(s) from Box 154, folder 3802 (Box 173, Folder 4386)
    - Photograph(s) from Box 154, folder 3803 (Box 173, Folder 4387)
    - Photograph(s) from Box 154, folder 3804 (Box 173, Folder 4388)
    - Photograph(s) from Box 154, folder 3805 (Box 173, Folder 4389)
    - Photograph(s) from Box 154, folder 3806 (Box 173, Folder 4390)
    - Photograph(s) from Box 154, folder 3807 (Box 173, Folder 4391)
    - Photograph(s) from Box 154, folder 3808 (Box 173, Folder 4392)
    - Photograph(s) from Box 154, folder 3809 (Box 173, Folder 4393)
    - Photograph(s) from Box 154, folder 3815 (Box 173, Folder 4394)
    - Photograph(s) from Box 154, folder 3816 (Box 173, Folder 4395)
    - Photograph(s) from Box 154, folder 3846 (Box 173, Folder 4396)
    - Photograph(s) from Box 154, folder 3847 (Box 173, Folder 4397)
    - Photograph(s) from Box 154, folder 3851 (Box 173, Folder 4398)
    - Photograph(s) from Box 154, folder 3848 (Box 173, Folder 4399)
    - Photograph(s) from Box 154, folder 3852 (Box 173, Folder 4400)
    - Photograph(s) from Box 154, folder 3853 (Box 173, Folder 4401)
    - Photograph(s) from Box 154, folder 3854 (Box 173, Folder 4402)
    - Photograph(s) from Box 154, folder 3855 (Box 173, Folder 4403)
    - Photograph(s) from Box 154, folder 3856 (Box 173, Folder 4404)
    - Photograph(s) from Box 154, folder 3857 (Box 173, Folder 4405)
    - Photograph(s) from Box 154, folder 3859 (Box 173, Folder 4406)
    - Photograph(s) from Box 154, folder 3860 (Box 173, Folder 4407)
    - Photograph(s) from Box 154, folder 3861 (Box 173, Folder 4408)
    - Photograph(s) from Box 154, folder 3862 (Box 173, Folder 4409)
    - Photograph(s) from Box 154, folder 3863 (Box 173, Folder 4410)
    - Photograph(s) from Box 147, folder 3439 (Box 173, Folder 4411)
    - Negative from Box 150, folder 3539a (Box 173, Folder 4412)